Soviet Union and Russia Pentecostal Subject Files, Inclusive: 1928-2006, Bulk: 1975-1983
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Samizdat, 1961-1988; 3
  - Pentecostal Believers Imprisonment. Ukraine, 1967-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Believers Imprisonment. Walter, Viktor, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices against Pentecostal Church. Refusal to Register, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices against Pentecostal Believers. Discrimination in Employment, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices against Pentecostal Believers. Discrimination in Education, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Oppressive Practices against Pentecostal Believers. Abuse of Psychiatry, 1975, 1978, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Oppressive Practices against Pentecostal Believers. Attacks in Media. General, 1974-1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Oppressive Practices against Pentecostal Believers. Attacks in Media. Starotitarovskaya (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Oppressive Practices against Pentecostal Believers. Attacks in Media. Starotitarovskaya (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Oppressive Practices against Pentecostal Believers. House Searches, 1971, 1981-1985 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Pentecostal Church Life. Preaching. Evangelism. Conversion, 1979, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Individual Pentecostal Clergy. Fedotov, Ivan, 1966-1982, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Individual Pentecostal Clergy. Smushko, Vladimir, 1985, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Individual Pentecostal Clergy. Vlasov, Anatoli, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Pentecostal Church. International Relations, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Pentecostal Church. Religious Activities Disapproved by the State. General, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Visit to the US Embassy, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. General, 1977, 1980-1981, 1987 1988, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (1 of 12), 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (2 of 12), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (3 of 12), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (4 of 12), 1978 May 25 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (5 of 6), 1978 August 25 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (6 of 12), 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (7 of 12), 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (8 of 12), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (9 of 12), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (10 of 12), 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (11 of 12), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals (12 of 12), 1986-1987, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals and Statements, 1979-1980, 1984, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Chernogorsk, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Chuguevka, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Nakhodka (1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Nakhodka (2 of 2), 1977-1979, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Starotitarovskaya (1 of 2), 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Starotitarovskaya (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Estonia, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Latvia, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Group Appeals. Lithuania, 1978, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals (1 of 3), 1974, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals (2 of 3), 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals (3 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Chernogorsk (1 of 7), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Chernogorsk (2 of 7), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Chernogorsk (3 of 7), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Chernogorsk (4 of 7), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Chernogorsk (5 of 7), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Chernogorsk (6 of 7), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Chernogorsk (7 of 7), 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Lidiia Voronina's Report on Visits to Pentecostal Communities, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals to Dmitrii Sakharov, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Chernogorsk. Vashchenko Family, 1974-1979, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Chuguevka, 1983, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Myski, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Nakhodka, 1977, 1984, 1987, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Novokuznetsk, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Starotitarovskaya, 1978-1979, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Belorussia, 1977, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Estonia, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Estonia. Gorelkin Family, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Latvia, 1977 September (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Lithuania, 1977-1980, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Lithuania. Bulakh Family, 1979-1982, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Lithuania. Vasilev Family, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Ukraine (1 of 3), 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Ukraine (2 of 3), 1980-1983, 1986-1988, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Ukraine (3 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Ukraine. Rovno Region, 1977-1980, 1987-1988, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Ukraine. Ternopol Region, 1977-1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Ukraine. Zakarpattia Region, 1977, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Appeals. Ukraine. Zaporozhzhia Region, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Ukraine. Kopot family, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Ukraine. Megediuk Family, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Evich Family, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Markov, Vladimir, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Individual Appeals. Timonin, Pavel and Gorelkina Liubov, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. List of 1,596 Individuals, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. List of 1,462 Individuals, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. List of Signatories of Complaint-Declaration to UNO (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. List of Signatories of Complaint-Declaration to UNO (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. List of Signatories of Complaint-Declaration to UNO (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. List of 32 Families Wishing to Emigrate, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Lists of Families Wishing to Emigrate (1 of 6), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Lists of Families Wishing to Emigrate (2 of 6), 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Lists of Families Wishing to Emigrate (3 of 6), 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Lists of Families Wishing to Emigrate (4 of 6), 1978-1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Lists of Families Wishing to Emigrate (5 of 6), 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Lists of Families Wishing to Emigrate (6 of 6), 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Pentecostal Believers Biographical Information under "Rights to Emigrate from the USSR" Committee (1 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Pentecostal Believers Biographical Information under "Rights to Emigrate from the USSR" Committee (2 of 2), 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Dossier "Vykhodi" (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Dossier "Vykhodi" (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Dossier "Vykhodi" (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Dossier "Vykhodi" (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Dossier "Vykhodi." English Translation (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Dossier "Vykhodi." English Translation (2 of 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Dossier "Vykhodi." Signed Copies of Appeals, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Emigration on Religious Grounds. Dossier "Vykhodi." Signed Copies of Appeals. English Translation, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Contacts with Foreigners, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. General, 1955, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Publications. Information Bulletin (1 of 3), 1977 November (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Publications. Information Bulletin No 3 (2 of 3), 1977 December-1978 January (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Publications. Information Bulletin No 4 (3 of 3), undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Publication. Khristianin (1 of 4), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Publication. Khristianin (2 of 4), undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Publication. Khristianin (3 of 4), undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Publication. Khristianin (4 of 4), undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Writings. Karpenko, Denis, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Writings. Stepanov, Vladimir, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Writings. Vlasov, Anatoli (1 of 2), 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Pentecostal Samizdat. Writings. Vlasov, Anatoli (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Pentecostal Church. Theology. Philosophy. Education, 1967, 1979-1980, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Pentecostal Church. Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations, 1980, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Pentecostal Church. Pronouncements on Secular Affairs, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Pentecostal Church. Art. Literature. Music. General, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Pentecostal Church. Children and Youth, 1979-1981 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Pentecostal Church. Sociology and Family, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Pentecostal Believers. Appeals, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 22)